

# **Daniel Clas**

Software Developer

### **Profile**

I am a 25 years old developer from Buenos Aires, Argentina, with full-time availability. I have worked for myself and as part of a team using Agile methodologies. My professional goal is to further my career in an innovative environment solving real problems with people that know more than I do.

## **Career Summary**

### **Full-stack Developer**

Santander | 2019 - 2020

- Part of the team that maintains and continually evolves the bank's company-oriented products, found on the public web portal and on every executive's workstation across the bank's branches
- Developed two different APIs used internally by different teams

### Full-stack Developer

Accenture | 2019 - 2020

- Developed and maintained a portfolio of applications used internally by the company's more than 500k employees around the globe
- Developed by my own initiative scripts to automate reports our team was in charge of delivering to other business areas of the company

### **E-commerce Developer**

Freelance | 2017 - 2018

- -Worked for other people helping them set up their shopify stores
- -Built and maintained my own stores, which demanded skills outside software development like sales and marketing

#### **Contact Me**



danielclas@outlook.es



+54 911 3184 7400



linkedin.com/in/danielclas/

### Languages I Speak

-Spanish: native tongue.

**-English**: bilingual, written and spoken. Certificates:

Cambridge FIRST, ETS' TOEFL

### **Education**

Tecnicatura Superior en Programación at Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

2019 - 2021. GPA: 8,8/10

## See My Work



github.com/danielclas



danielclas.com

### **Technologies I Can Work With**

- -Front-end technologies: Angular, HTML/CSS, Javascript/jQuery
- -Back-end technologies: C, C#, PHP, Kotlin, Node.js, Java
- -Mobile technologies: Flutter
- -Other tools: AWS (Lambda, Dynamo), SQL, MongoDB, Shopify, Firestore, Postman, Git

#### **Character References**

**Matias Hamie** 

Peer at university

Email: mnhamie@gmail.com

### Diego D'alairac

Tech Lead at Santander Email: diegodalairac@gmail.com